<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Untitled RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Untitled RSS Feed]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylan/node-rss</link><generator>NodeJS RSS Module</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 17:26:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Tom Wilson on NodeJS]]></title><description><![CDATA[<h5>Quoted from Tom Wilson ( <a href="https://github.com/twilson63">https://github.com/twilson63</a> ), President and Lead Technologist @ Jack Russell Software ( <a href="http://jackhq.com">http://jackhq.com</a> )</h5> <br>

 <p>"I had a blast at NodeSummit.  I am real excited about NodeJS.  It was crazy all the things that are going on.  In my mind it is a full shift into what I believe will be the future of software!</p>  <ul><li>Applications composed of small components</li><li>Applications that can run on 1000 cpu machines</li><li>Presentation focused on the client, server focused on JSON/HTTP interfaces </li></ul> <p>  Javascript Everywhere!</p>  <p>  I think any developer will be a fool to overlook this technology.  IMO it is a huge technology shift and will be the norm in 2 years.  Async programming style is the reality and sync is close to dead.  I think/hope other languages will re-invent themselves, but it is not so much a language issue as much as a paradigm shift and the fact that processors can't double anymore.  Threaded programming is not the answer, it is too hard for a few and a mirage for the masses.  As it approaches load, the resources and time consumed trying to troubleshoot race conditions and other threaded stuff under the hood is beyond the creators of most apps.  Learning to break your application into solid loosely coupled pieces is the right thing to do at point of design!  Most current languages are not focused on making async programming enjoyable, they are focused on hiding the fact you are doing async programming and that is just as bad as StupidSense on an IDE."</p>  <p><img src="tom-wilson-on-nodejs/jackdog.png" alt="Jack Russell Software" title="Jack Russell Software"></p>]]></description><link>http://undefined/tom-wilson-on-nodejs</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://undefined/tom-wilson-on-nodejs</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Kris Windham]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 20:42:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[playing with nodejitsu]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>I recently received my beta invite to nodejitsu PaaS.</p>  <p><a href="http://nodejitsu.com/">http://nodejitsu.com/</a></p>  <p>I have to say that as far as a beta goes, this is one of the smoothest
things I have ever worked with. I really like how all I have to type is
<em>jitsu deploy</em> inside the app directory.  jitsu CLI does everything for you from creating the app, figuring out the subdomain and deploying the app to nodejitsu. It even creates the package.json files for you with all dependencies and versioning.  Node 0.6.9 apps will run fine on nodejitsu.</p>  <p>I am still trying to wrap my head
around flatiron ( <a href="http://flatironjs.org/">http://flatironjs.org/</a> ), but have found that the tools that nodejitsu is offering work very well in general and hope to have the time to continue playing around with everything they have to offer. Their documentation is incredible.  I do wish that I could see some more real world examples of how to work with flatiron, union and director, but given the time I should be able to
figure it out without too much hand holding.  I hope nodejitsu is very successful and this business model continues to flourish and be an option for me to use in the future for deployment of node apps.  Thanks a lot for all of the fantastic work you have done.  Hopefully Nodejitsu will continue to focus only on NodeJS and Javascript and not take the direction of Heroku since the Saleforce takeover.  Heroku is now trying to support way too many languages. I like the idea of doing one thing and doing it well.  This invite has really gotten me stoked on working with NodeJs again after quite a number of weeks of not writing any code at all.
Perfect timing guys.  </p>  <p><img src="playing-with-nodejitsu/nodejitsu.png" alt="Nodejitsu" title="Nodejitsu"></p> ]]></description><link>http://undefined/playing-with-nodejitsu</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://undefined/playing-with-nodejitsu</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Kris Windham]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 16:40:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Starting with blacksmith]]></title><description><![CDATA[<p>Getting started with Blacksmith.  <a href="http://blacksmith.jit.su/all-pages">http://blacksmith.jit.su/all-pages</a></p>  <p>Just getting started with nodejitsu and really like the idea of this
static site generator for a blog.  I was unable to get it to run without
explicitly stating http-server v0.2.x in my package.json.  v0.3 does not seem to work with Blacksmith.</p>  <p><img src="starting-with-blacksmith/blacksmith.png" alt="Blacksmith" title="Blacksmith"></p> ]]></description><link>http://undefined/starting-with-blacksmith</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://undefined/starting-with-blacksmith</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Kris Windham]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 21:03:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>